A Guide to the University of Virginia Hospital Executive Director's Office (HEDO) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- CONSTRUCTION OF VEPCO SUBSTATION: CORRESPONDENCE 1961, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 19:018)
- CONSTRUCION, VIVARIUM: CORRESPONDENCE & PROJECT SCHEDULES 1959 - 1964, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 19:019)
- CONSTRUCTION, WAGE RATES: CORRESPONDENCE 1957 - 1958, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 19:020)
- CONSTRUCTION OF WEST ADDITION: CORRESPONDENCE 1954 - 1960, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 19:021)
- MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE RE: CONSTRUCTION AND RENOVATION 1954 - 1982, TL, TLS (2), AMs (Box-folder 19:022)
- REVISED COST ESTIMATES FOR HOSPITAL ALTERATIONS AND ADDITIONS 1951, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 19:023)
- CONSUMER COMMENT: NEWS OF INTEREST TO LOCAL CONSUMERS February 1971-April 1971, Leaflets (Box-folder 19:024)
- MEDICAL ILLUSTRATION: CORRESPONDENCE 1955 - 1969, TL, TLS (2), Newsclippings (Box-folder 19:025)
- SOLUTION ROOM PRODUCTION REPORTS 1966 - 1971, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 19:026)
- STOREROOM REQUISITION EXPENSE 1955 - 1959, TL, TMs (Box-folder 19:027)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1948 - July 1953, TL (2), TLS (3), TMs (Box-folder 19:028)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE August 1953 - December, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 19:029)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1954, TL (2), TLS (2), AN (Box-folder 19:030)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1955 - 1956, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 19:031)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1957 - 1958, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 19:032)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1959 - 1961, TL (2), TLS (3) (Box-folder 19:033)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1962 - 1963, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 19:034)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1964, TL, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 19:035)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1965 - 1966, TL (2), TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 19:036)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1967, TL (2), TLS (2), AMs (Box-folder 19:037)
- BUILDINGS & GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE March 1968 - August 1968, TL (2), TLS (2), TN (Box-folder 19:038)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE August 1968 - Sept. 1968, TL (2), TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 19:039)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE January 1969, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 19:040)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE September 1969 - December, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 19:041)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1970, ANS, TLS (2), TL (2), TN, TMs (Box-folder 19:042)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE 1971, ANS, TNS, TL, TLS, Newsclipping (Box-folder 19:043)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE January 1972 - April 1978, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 19:044)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: CORRESPONDENCE May 1978, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 19:045)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: MAINTENANCE DEPARTMENT PROGRESS REPORTS September 1956 - Oct 1956, TL, TMs (Box-folder 19:046)
- THIRD REFRESHER COURSE IN GENERAL MEDICINE, UVA, DEPARTMENT OF MEDICINE June 3-15, 1946, TMs (Box-folder 20:034)
- REFERSHER COURSE IN GENERAL MEDICINE, UVA, DEPARTMENT OF MEDICINE June 16-21, 1941, TMs (Box-folder 20:033)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: MONTHLY REPORT OF DIVISION REPORTS January 1975 - May 1975, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 20:001)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: MONTHLY REPORT OF DIVISION PROJECTS June 1975-September 1975, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 20:002)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: MONTHLY REPORTS OF DIVISION PROJECTS 1975, TLS, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 20:003)
- BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS: REPORT ON MEDICAL SCHOOL & HOSPITAL MAINTENANCE PROBLEMS 1960, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 20:004)
- MAINTENANCE TO HOSPITAL ROUTINE December 1952 - 1953, ANS, TMs (Box-folder 20:005)
  FROM BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS FILE
- MAINTENANCE TO HOSPITAL ROUTINE 1954, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 20:006)
- MAINTENANCE TO HOSPITAL 1955, TMs (Box-folder 20:007)
- ROUTINE MAINTENANCE TO HOSPITAL 1956, TMs (Box-folder 20:008)
- ROUTINE MAINTENANCE TO HOSPITAL 1957, TMs (Box-folder 20:009)
- ROUTINE MAINTENANCE TO HOSPITAL 1958, TMs (Box-folder 20:010)
- ROUTINE MAINTENANCE TO HOSPITAL 1959, TMs (Box-folder 20:011)
- ROUTINE MAINTENANCE TO HOSPITAL 1960, TMs (Box-folder 20:012)
- ROUTINE MAINTENANCE TO HOSPITAL 1961 - 1963, TMs (Box-folder 20:013)
- ROUTINE MAINTENANCE TO HOSPITAL 1965 - 1971, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 20:014)
- SPECIFICATIONS FOR SWITCHGEAR FOR HOSPITAL SUBSTATION August 1, 1955, TMs (Box-folder 20:015)
- REPORT OF SPECIAL INCIDENT, RE: LUMEX INVALID WALKER November 1971, TLS, Questionnaire (Box-folder 20:016)
- USING HAS DATA TO MAKE COMPARISONS, THEN EVALUATE YOUR PLANT OPERATIONS DEPARTMENT 1967, Leaflet (Box-folder 20:017)
- PHOTOGRAPHS FROM BUILDINGS AND GROUNDS FILE RE: DEFECTIVE FURNACE AND FIRE September 1968, 8 B&W photographs (Box-folder 20:018)
- THE UVA HOSPITAL: ITS FIRST FIFTY YEARS (FIRST CHAPTER) 1955, TLS, ALS, TMs (Box-folder 20:019)
- UVA HOSPITAL: ITS FIRST FIFTY YEARS (CHAPTERS 2 & 3) 1955, TMs (Box-folder 20:020)
- UVA HOSPITAL: ITS FIRST FIFTY YEARS (CHAPTERS 4 & 5) 1955, TMs (Box-folder 20:021)
- UVA HOSPITAL: ITS FIRST FIFTY YEARS (CHAPTERS 6 & 7) 1955, TMs (Box-folder 20:022)
- UVA HOSPITAL: ITS FIRST FIFTY YEARS (CHAPTERS 8 & 9) 1955, TMs (Box-folder 20:023)
- UVA HOSPITAL: ITS FIRST FIFTY YEARS (CHAPTERS 10 & 11) 1955, TM (Box-folder 20:024)
- UVA HOSPITAL: ITS FIRST FIFTY YEARS (CHAPTERS 12 & 13) 1955, TMs (Box-folder 20:025)
- UVA HOSPITAL: ITS FIRST FIFTY YEARS(CHAPTERS 14 & 15) 1955, TMs (Box-folder 20:026)
- UVA HOSPITAL: ITS FIRST FIFTY YEARS (CHAPTERS 16 & 17) 1955, TMs (Box-folder 20:027)
- AUTHORISATION TO OPERATE DISTILLING APPARATUS March 30, 1929, TLS (Box-folder 20:028)
  FROM ALCOHOL FILE
- ALCOHOL: CORRESPONDENCE 1938 - 1939, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 20:029)
- ALCOHOL: CORRESPONDENCE 1940, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 20:030)
- ALCOHOL: CORRESPONDENCE 1941 - 1954, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 20:031)
- HOSPITAL PERMITS AND APPLICATIONS RE: ALCOHOL 1938 - 1940, TN, Applications Invoice (Box-folder 20:032)
  TRANSPORTATION AND USE OF ALCOHOL
- UVA HOSPITAL HOUSKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE 1962 - 1963, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 21:001)
- UVA HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE 1964, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 21:002)
- UVA HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE 1965, TL, TLS (2), ALS (Box-folder 21:003)
- UVA HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE January 1966 - May 1966, AL, AMs, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 21:004)
- UVA HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE June 1966 - December 1966, ALS, TLS (Box-folder 21:005)
- UVA HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE January 1967 March 1967, TL (2), TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 21:006)
- UVA HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE June 1967, TL, TLS (3), TMs (Box-folder 21:007)
- UVA HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE July 1967 - December 1967, TL (2), TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 21:008)
- UVA HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE January 1968 - April 1968, TL (2), TLS, TMs (Box-folder 21:009)
- HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE May 1968 - July 1968, TL (2), TLS (Box-folder 21:010)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE August - December 1968, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 21:011)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE January 1969, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 21:012)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: CORRESPONDENCE February 1969 - August, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 21:013)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING REPORTS 1963 - 1964, TMs (Box-folder 21:014)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING REPORTS AND BUDGET 1965, AMs (Box-folder 21:015)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING REPORTS AND BUDGETS 1966, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 21:016)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING REPORTS AND BUDGETS 1967, TMs (Box-folder 21:017)
- REPORT ON RACIAL COMPOSITION OF HOUSEKEEPING STAFF 1967, TMs (Box-folder 21:018)
- HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: REPORTS AND BUDGETS 1968, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 21:018)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: REPORTS 1969, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 21:019)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: WAGE RATES AND PROCEDURES 19655, TMs (Box-folder 21:020)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: WAGE RATES AND EMPLOYEE LISTS 1967, TMs (Box-folder 21:021)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT: WAGE RATES AND PROCEDURES 1968, TMs (Box-folder 21:022)
- PROPOSED SUPERVISORY ORGANIZATIONAL CHART: HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT 1965, TMs (Box-folder 21:023)
- HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT INSPECTION CHECK LISTS No date, TMs (Box-folder 21:024)
- LISTS OF DUTIES FOR MAIDS AND JANITORS IN THE NEWBORN SPECIAL CARE UNIT 1967, TMs (Box-folder 21:025)
- HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING OPERATIONS FROM HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING FILE 1969, TL, TMs (Box-folder 21:026)
- DAY SHIFT SCHEDULE FROM HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT FILE 1969, TMs (Box-folder 21:027)
- QUALIFICATIONS AND DUTIES OF JANITORS AND MAIDS 1953, TMs (Box-folder 21:028)
  FROM HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING FILE
- THE HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT OF THE UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA February 1, 1957, TMs (Box-folder 21:029)
- A TALE OF TWO CITIES: THE NEED FOR ENGINEERED MAINTENANCE September 30, 1963, TMs (Box-folder 21:030)
  FROM HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT FILE
- WHAT MANAGEMENT EXPECTS FROM A HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT September 20, 1963, TMs (Box-folder 21:031)
- OPERATING ROOM CLEANING PROCEDURES 1965, TMs (Box-folder 21:032)
  FROM HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT FILE
- HOUSEKEEPING: STAFF UTILIZATION AND CONTROL PROGRAM April 1965, TMs (Box-folder 21:033)
- CONTINUOUS ENVIRONMENTAL SANITATION 1967, TMs (Box-folder 21:034)
- OBJECTIVES OF MANAGING A WORK FORCE 1967, TMs (Box-folder 21:034)
- TRAINING HOUSEKEEPING EMPLOYEES 1968, TMs (Box-folder 21:036)
- A QUALITY CONTROL PLAN FOR HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT 1968, TMs (Box-folder 21:037)
- FINAL EXAMINATION: HOUSEKEEPING AIDE TRAINING PROGRAM 1968, TMs (Box-folder 21:038)
- DIAGRAMS OF HOSPITAL SUPPLIES FROM HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT 1969, Xerox drawings (Box-folder 21:039)
- THREE BASICPROCEDURES FOR HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING No date, Booklet (Box-folder 21:040)
- THE WORK MANUAL OF THE EXECUTIVE HOUSEKEEPER OF THE HOSPITAL 1965, Booklet (Box-folder 21:041)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS FROM HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING FILE 1962 - 1968, Pamphlets and Leaflets, 1 photograph (Box-folder 21:042)
- MISCELLANEOUS ITEMS FROM THE HOSPITAL HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT FILE 1963 - 1968, AMs, TMs, newsclippings, invoice (Box-folder 21:043)
- HOUSE STAFF ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1971, AN, AMs, TL (2) (Box-folder 22:001)
- HOUSE STAFF ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1972, TL (2), AN, TMs (Box-folder 22:002)
- HOUSE STAFF ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1973, TLS, TL (2) (Box-folder 22:003)
- HOUSE STAFF ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1974, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 22:004)
- HOUSE STAFF ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1975, TL (2), TLS (Box-folder 22:005)
- HOUSE STAFF ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1971, TMs (Box-folder 22:006)
- HOUSE STAFF ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1972, TMs (Box-folder 22:007)
- HOUSE STAFF ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1973, TMs (Box-folder 22:008)
- HOUSE STAFF ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1974, TMs (Box-folder 22:009)
- HOUSE STAFF ASSOCIATION EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1975, TMs (Box-folder 22:010)
- FACULTY-HOUSE STAFF COMMITTEE MINUTES September - October 1970, TMs, TLS, TL, Charts (Box-folder 22:011)
- FACULTY-HOUSE STAFF COMMITTEE MINUTES November - December 1970, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 22:012)
- FACULTY-HOUSE STAFF COMMITTEE MINUTES January - February 1971, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 22:013)
- HOUSE STAFF-ATTENDING STAFF LIASON COMMITTEE March 1971-December 1971, Ams, TMs (Box-folder 22:014)
  FORMERLY FACULTY-HOUSE STAFF COMMITTEE
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1965 - 1966, TL, TLS (Box-folder 22:015)
  LISTS OF EMPLOYEES EXPOSED TO INFECTIOUS PATIENTS
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1961 - 1962, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 22:016)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1963, TL, ALS, TLS (Box-folder 22:017)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1964, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 22:018)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1965, TL, TLS (Box-folder 22:019)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1965, TL, TMs (Box-folder 22:020)
  LETTERS FROM T.B. INFECTIONS COMMITTEE
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1966, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 22:021)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1967, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 22:022)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1968, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 22:023)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1969, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 22:024)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1970, TL, TMs, TLS (2) (Box-folder 22:025)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1972, AN, TL, TLS (2), Charts (Box-folder 22:027)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1973, TL (2), TLS (2), Chart (Box-folder 22:028)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1974, TL (2), TLS (2), AN, TMs, Chart (Box-folder 22:029)
- INFECTION COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1975, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 22:030)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1964 - 1965, TMs (Box-folder 23:001)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1962 - 1963, TMs (Box-folder 23:002)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1966, TMs (Box-folder 23:003)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1967, TLS, Articles, TMs (Box-folder 23:004)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1968, TMs (Box-folder 23:005)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1969, TMs (Box-folder 23:006)
  PROCEDURES FOR ISOLATION OF PATIENTS
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES February 1969 - December, AMs, TMs, Article (Box-folder 23:007)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1970, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 23:008)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1971 - September, TMs (Box-folder 23:009)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES October 1971 - December, TMs (Box-folder 23:010)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1972, TMs, Article Reprint (Box-folder 23:011)
  SERIAL TUBERCULIN TESTING AND ISONIAZID THERAPY IN GENERAL HOSPITAL EMPLOYEES
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES February 1972, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:012)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES March 1972 - June 1972, TL, TMs (Box-folder 23:013)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES July 1972 - December 1972, TLS, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:014)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1973 - May 1973, AMs, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:015)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES June 1973 - December 1973, AMs, TMs, TLS, Charts (Box-folder 23:016)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1974 - May 1974, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:017)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES June 1974-September 1974, TMs, Articles (Box-folder 23:018)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES October 1974 - December, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:019)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1975 - March 1975, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:020)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES April 1975 - May 1975, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:021)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES June 1975 - October 1975, TMs (Box-folder 23:022)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES November 1975 - December, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:023)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1976 - February, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:024)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES March 1976 - April 1976, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:025)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES May 1976 - June 1976, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:026)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES September 1976 - October, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:027)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES November 1976 - December, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:028)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1977 - February, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:029)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES March 1977 - April 1977, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:030)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES May 1977 - June 1977, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:031)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES September 1977 - October, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:032)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES November 1977 - December, TLS, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:033)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1978, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:034)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES February 1978 - March, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:035)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES April 1978 - May 1978, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:036)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES September 1978 - October, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:037)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES November 1978 - December, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:038)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1979, TLS, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 23:039)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES February 1979, TMs (Box-folder 23:040)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES March 1979, TMs (Box-folder 23:041)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES April 1979, TMs (Box-folder 23:042)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES May 1979, TMs (Box-folder 24:001)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES June 1979, TMs, Charts (Box-folder 24:002)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES September 1979, TMs (Box-folder 24:003)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES November 1979, TMs (Box-folder 24:004)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES December 1979, TMs (Box-folder 24:005)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE: MINUTES 1962 - 1963, TL, TMs (Box-folder 24:006)
- SUMMARIES OF REPORTS OF CHARTED INFECTIONS AT UVA HOSPITAL 1964, TL, TMs (Box-folder 24:007)
- ISOLATION SURVEYS 1966 - 1967, TMs (Box-folder 24:008)
- HOUSEKEEPING DEPARTMENT REPORTS SENT TO INFECTIONS COMMITTEE 1969, TMs (Box-folder 24:009)
- PROCEDURES FOR ISOLATION OF PATIENTS, UVA HOSPITAL N. D., TMs (Box-folder 24:010)
- LISTS OF INFECTIOUS DISEASES TO BE REPORTED TO THE HEALTH DEPARTMENT N.D., 1972, ANS, TMs (Box-folder 24:011)
  FROM INFECTIONS COMMITTEE FILE
- ISOLATION PROCEDURES N.D., Pamphlet (Box-folder 24:012)
- ISOLATION PROCEDURES N.D., TMs (Box-folder 24:013)
- GUIDELINES FOR PROPHYLAXIS OF VIRAL HEPATITIS N.D., TMs (Box-folder 24:014)
- PROCEDURES FOR ISOLATION OF PATIENTS May 1963, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 24:015)
- MASK OPERATION N.D., TMs (Box-folder 24:016)
  FROM INFECTION COMMITTEE FILES
- INFECTION COMMITTEE JOB SUMMARY AND COMMENTS 1967, TMs (Box-folder 24:017)
- OUTLINE FOR SURVEILLANCE AND CONTROL OF NOSCOMIAL INFECTIONS 1970, AMs, TMs, Clippings (Box-folder 24:018)
- WHAT ARE CLEAN HOSPITAL FLOORS? 1970, TMs (Box-folder 24:019)
- UVA MEDICAL CENTER ISOLATION PROCEDURE AND INFECTION CONTROL MANUAL July 1, 1971, TMs (Box-folder 24:020)
- ISOLATION PROCEDURES March 1971, TL, TMs, Flyers (Box-folder 24:021)
- TEMPERATURE, PULSE AND RESPIRATION 1972, TMs (Box-folder 24:022)
- THE TUBERCULOSIS CONTROL COMMITTEE 1972, TMs, TNs (Box-folder 24:023)
- CONTROL OF HOSPITAL-ACQUIRED INFECTIONS 1973, TMs (Box-folder 24:024)
- UVA MEDICAL CENTER: ISOLATION PROCEDURE & INFECTION CONTROL MANUAL 1973 - 1974, TLS, Booklet (Box-folder 24:025)
- TOTAL PARENTERAL NUTRITION (HYPERALIMENTATION) December 1974, TL, TMs (Box-folder 24:026)
- TOTAL PARENTERAL NUTRITION (HYPERALIMENTATION) January 1975, TL, TMs (Box-folder 24:027)
- TOTAL PARENTERAL NUTRITION August 1975, TL, TMs (Box-folder 24:028)
- A SURVEY OF A NOTED HOSPITAL FOR THE IMPROVEMENT OF THE CONTROL OF CROSS INFECTION N.D., Booklet (Box-folder 24:029)
  FROM INFECTION COMMITTEE FILE
- SUGGESTED ISOLATION TECHNIQUE FOR USE WITH ISOLATION CART N.D., TMs (Box-folder 24:030)
  BY AMERICAN HOSPITAL SUPPLY CORPORATION
- STERILIZATION STANDARDS May 25, 1962, Article (Box-folder 24:031)
  ADDRESS GIVEN AT MIDDLE ATLANTIC HOSPITAL ASSEMBLY
- FDA VIEW OF PROBLEMS ASSOCIATED WITH PACKAGING, STORING & DISTRIBUTING STERILE MEDICAL DEVICES May 1967, TMs (Box-folder 24:032)
- ISOLATION TECHNIQUES FOR THE GENERAL HOSPITAL 1968, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 24:033)
  GOVERNMENT PUBLICATION
- ISOLATION TECHNIQUES FOR USE IN HOSPITALS 1970, Booklet & adhesive stickers (Box-folder 24:034)
- HEXACHLOROPHENE USAGE & STAPHYLOCOCCAL DISEASE 1972, TL, TMs (Box-folder 24:035)
- HOSPITAL INFECTIONS 1961 - 1971, Articles (Box-folder 24:036)
- HOSPITAL INFECTIONS 1962 - 1968, Articles (Box-folder 24:037)
- HOSPITAL INFECTIONS 1970 - 1971, Articles (Box-folder 24:038)
- HOSPITAL INFECTIONS 1958, 1969, 1974, Leaflets, Newsletter (Box-folder 24:039)
- CONFERENCE PROGRAMS 1970, 1975, TMs, Leaflets (Box-folder 24:040)
- PRODUCT INFORMATION & ADVERTISEMENTS FROM MEDICAL SUPPLY COMPANIES N.D., 1962 - 1966, Pamphlets, Leaflets, Booklets, Photographs (2) (Box-folder 25:001)
- INFECTION SURVEILLANCE FORMS N.D., TMs (Box-folder 25:002)
- INVOICES FROM INFECTIONS COMMITTEE FILE 1974, Invoices (Box-folder 25:003)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE FILE: MISCELLANEOUS N.D., 1963 - 1976, Leaflets, Clippings, TMs (Box-folder 25:004)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1971 - 1972, TL, TLS (Box-folder 25:005)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE 1973, TL, TLS (Box-folder 25:006)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE January 1974 - April 1974, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 25:007)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE May 1974 - December 1974, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 25:008)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE January 1975 - June 1975, AMs, TMs, TL, TLS (Box-folder 25:009)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES January - February 1972, TMs (Box-folder 25:010)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES March 1972, TMs (Box-folder 25:011)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES April 1972, TMs (Box-folder 25:012)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES May 1972, TMs (Box-folder 25:013)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA AND MINUTES June 1972, TMs (Box-folder 25:014)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES July 1972, TMs (Box-folder 25:015)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES September 1972, TMs (Box-folder 25:016)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES November 1972, TMs (Box-folder 25:017)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES December 1972, TMs (Box-folder 25:018)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES December 1972, TMs (Box-folder 25:018)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES January - February 1973, TMs (Box-folder 25:019)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES March 1973, TMs (Box-folder 24:020)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA & MINUTES May 1973, TMs (Box-folder 25:021)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES June 1973, TMs (Box-folder 25:022)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES July 1973, TMs (Box-folder 25:023)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES September - December 1973, TMs (Box-folder 25:024)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE January - February 1974, TMs (Box-folder 25:025)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES March 1974 - April 1974, TMs (Box-folder 25:026)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES May 1974 - June 1974, TMs (Box-folder 25:027)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES July 1974 - December 1974, TMs (Box-folder 25:028)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE July 1975 - December 1975, TLS (Box-folder 25:029)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE January 1976 - March 1976, TL (2), TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 25:030)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE April 1976 - May 1976, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 25:031)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE June 1976 - July 1976, AN, TN, ALS, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 25:032)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: CORRESPONDENCE September 1976, TMs, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 25:033)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES January - February 1975, TMs (Box-folder 26:001)
  MEETING HELD 7 JANUARY 1975
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES April 1975 - May 1975, TMs (Box-folder 26:002)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES June 1975 - July 1975, TMs (Box-folder 26:003)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA AND MINUTES September 1975, TL, TMs (Box-folder 26:004)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES October - November 1975, TMs (Box-folder 26:005)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA AND MINUTES December 1975, TMs, TL, TLS (Box-folder 26:006)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES January 1976, TMs (Box-folder 26:007)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES February 1976, TMs (Box-folder 26:008)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES March 1976, TMs (Box-folder 26:009)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: MINUTES April 1976, TMs (Box-folder 16:010)
- MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE: AGENDA AND MINUTES May 1976, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 26:011)